This is a combination I know many of you all have been waiting for.
I am here with the Representative Jasmine Crockett of Dallas, Tejas.
Hey, y'all.
Known for keeping it a hundo, okay?
A buck fifty when she is in that house.
My favorite line is, you know this?
This committee run my pressure up, okay?
So we are here and we will be discussing side effects of gathering the government
because that's what you'll be doing.
But I would love to get you all's questions for Representative Crockett.
If they can be questions that are specifically related to the work she does,
to government, et cetera, drop them in the comments
because I know that we are all trying to understand a bit more about how this works
so we can change to make it work for the better.